Finding Aid for the J. Warren Perry Collection of Ballet Photographs, circa 1910-1960
State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Library
- People, circa 1910-1960, I.; Boxes 1-4 (Items 1-250)
  - Mary Ellen Moylan as Agatha the White Cat in Demoiselles de la nuit, undated, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Owen, Walter E., 1896-1963 (Box 3, Item JWPB150)
  - Mary Ellen Moylan as Odile, the Black Swan, undated, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Owen, Walter E., 1896-1963 (Box 3, Item JWPB151)
  - Mary Ellen Moylan as the Ballerina in Soirée, between 1955 and 1957, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; LeBlang, Sedge (Box 3, Item JWPB152)
  - Nadia Nerina as Odette-Odile in Swan Lake, undated, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 3, Item JWPB153)
  - Nadia Nerina, undated, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 3, Item JWPB154)
  - Nadia Nerina as Sylvia, undated, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 3, Item JWPB155)
  - Nadia Nerina as Princess Aurora in Sleeping Beauty, undated, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 3, Item JWPB156)
  - Nadia Nerina as the Faded Beauty and Leslie Edwards as the Hypnotist in Noctambules, 1956, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Dunne, Michael (Box 3, Item JWPB157)
  - Nadia Nerina as the Faded Beauty and Leslie Edwards as the Hypnotist in Noctambules, 1956, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Dunne, Michael (Box 3, Item JWPB158)
  - Nadia Nerina and David Blair in Fille mal Gardée, 1960, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 3, Item JWPB159)
  - Nina Novak, undated, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 3, Item JWPB160)
  - Nina Novak, undated, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 3, Item JWPB161)
  - Nina Novak, undated, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 3, Item JWPB162)
  - Nina Novak, undated, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 3, Item JWPB163)
  - Annette Page, undated, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 3, Item JWPB164)
  - Annette Page as Odette in Le Lac des cygnes, undated, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 3, Item JWPB165)
  - Annette Page as Odette and Ronald Hynd as Siegfried in Le Lac des Cygnes, undated, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 3, Item JWPB166)
  - Annette Page as Odette and Ronald Hynd as Siegfried in Le Lac des Cygnes, undated, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 3, Item JWPB167)
  - Ruth Page portrait, undated, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Muray, Arthur (Box 3, Item JWPB168)
  - Ruth Page in Birthday of the Infanta, undated, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Daquerre, Chicago (Box 3, Item JWPB169)
  - Ruth Page in Etude, with music by Chopin, undated, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Muray, Arthur (Box 3, Item JWPB170)
  - Ruth Page as Peter Pan, undated, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Mishkin, Herman (Box 3, Item JWPB171)
  - Ruth Page as Queen Shemakhan in Le Coq d'or, undated, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Irigoyent, B. de (Box 3, Item JWPB172)
  - Ruth Page in The Bartered Bride, undated, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Goldberg (New York, N.Y.) (Box 3, Item JWPB173)
  - Merle Park as Lise in La Fille Mal Gardée, 1960, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 3, Item JWPB174)
  - Merle Park as Lise in La Fille Mal Gardée, 1960, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 3, Item JWPB175)
  - Anna Pavlova, 1910, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Mishkin, Herman (Box 3, Item JWPB176)
  - Maya Plisetskaya as Odette in Swan Lake, undated, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 3, Item JWPB177)
  - Janet Reed, 1954, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 3, Item JWPB178)
  - Janet Reed, undated, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 3, Item JWPB179)
  - Janet Reed as the Countess and Roy Tobias as the Count in the Unicorn, the Gorgon, and the Manticore, 1957, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 3, Item JWPB180)
  - Jerome Robbins, undated, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 3, Item JWPB181)
  - Jerome Robbins as the Prodigal Son, 1950, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Carswell, Ed (Box 3, Item JWPB182)
  - Jerome Robbins, Janet Reed, John Kriza, Muriel Bentley, Harold Lang, and Rex Cooper in Fancy Free, 1944, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 3, Item JWPB183)
  - Ruth St. Denis, 1922, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Bigelow, Lou Goodale (Box 3, Item JWPB184)
  - Lupe Serrano, undated, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 3, Item JWPB185)
  - Lupe Serrano as Clorinda in The Combat, 1957, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 3, Item JWPB186)
  - Lupe Serrano in Designs with Strings, 1956, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Seymour, Maurice, 1904- (Box 3, Item JWPB187)
  - Lupe Serrano and John Kriza in Designs with Strings, 1956, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Seymour, Maurice, 1904- (Box 3, Item JWPB188)
  - Brian Shaw as the Soldier in Noctambules, 1956, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Dunne, Michael (Box 3, Item JWPB189)
  - Brian Shaw the Blue Skater in Les Patineurs, undated, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; LeBlang, Sedge (Box 3, Item JWPB190)
  - Ted Shawn, undated, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Witzel (Box 4, Item JWPB191)
  - Moira Shearer, undated, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 4, Item JWPB192)
  - Moira Shearer as Titania in Midsummer Night's Dream, 1954, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 4, Item JWPB193)
  - Moira Shearer as Titania and Robert Helpmann as Oberon in Midsummer Night's Dream, 1954, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 4, Item JWPB194)
  - Mia Slavenska, undated, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Constantine, 1913-1982 (Box 4, Item JWPB195)
  - Mia Slavenska, undated, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Constantine, 1913-1982 (Box 4, Item JWPB196)
  - Mia Slavenska, undated, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Constantine, 1913-1982 (Box 4, Item JWPB197)
  - Michael Somes as Ivan Tsarevitch in The Firebird, 1954, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Rogers, Houston (Box 4, Item JWPB198)
  - Michael Somes as Prince Siegfried and Rowena Jackson as Odette in Le Lac des Cygnes, undated, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 4, Item JWPB199)
  - Barbara Steele, undated, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Seymour, Maurice, 1904- (Box 4, Item JWPB200)
  - Raisa Struchkova in Walpurgisnacht, 1956, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 4, Item JWPB201)
  - Raisa Struchkova in Walpurgisnacht, 1956, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 4, Item JWPB202)
  - Raisa Struchkova and Alexander Lapauri in Walpurgisnacht, 1956, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 4, Item JWPB203)
  - Marina Svetlova, undated, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Seymour, Maurice, 1904- (Box 4, Item JWPB204)
  - Maria Tallchief and Edward Bigelow in Orpheus, undated, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 4, Item JWPB205)
  - Maria Tallchief and Nicholas Magallanes in Orpheus, 1950, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 4, Item JWPB206)
  - Maria Tallchief as Eurydice in Orpheus, undated, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 4, Item JWPB207)
  - Maria Tallchief, undated, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Seymour, Maurice, 1904- (Box 4, Item JWPB208)
  - Maria Tallchief in Swan Lake, 1951, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 4, Item JWPB209)
  - Maria Tallchief and André Eglevsky in Swan Lake, 1951, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 4, Item JWPB210)
  - Maria Tallchief and André Eglevsky in Pas de Dix, 1955, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 4, Item JWPB211)
  - Maria Tallchief and Nicholas Magallanes in Allegro Brillante, 1956, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Fehl, Fred (Box 4, Item JWPB212)
  - Maria Tallchief and Nicholas Magallanes in Allegro Brillante, 1956, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Fehl, Fred (Box 4, Item JWPB213)
  - Maria Tallchief and Nicholas Magallanes in Bourrée fantasque, 1949, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 4, Item JWPB214)
  - Maria Tallchief and Nicholas Magallanes in Bourrée fantasque, 1949, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 4, Item JWPB215)
  - Maria Tallchief and Francisco Moncion in The Firebird, 1949, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 4, Item JWPB216)
  - Maria Tallchief and Francisco Moncion in The Firebird, 1949, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 4, Item JWPB217)
  - Maria Tallchief and Francisco Moncion in The Firebird, 1949, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 4, Item JWPB218)
  - Maria Tallchief, Melissa Hayden, and André Eglevsky in Pas de Trois, 1951, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 4, Item JWPB219)
  - Maria Tallchief, Patricia Wilde, and André Eglevsky in Pas de Trois, 1955, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Fehl, Fred (Box 4, Item JWPB220)
  - Maria Tallchief in Scotch Symphony, 1952, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 4, Item JWPB221)
  - Maria Tallchief and André Eglevsky in Scotch Symphony, 1952, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 4, Item JWPB222)
  - Maria Tallchief and André Eglevsky in Scotch Symphony, 1952, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 4, Item JWPB223)
  - Maria Tallchief and André Eglevsky in Scotch Symphony, 1952, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Owen, Walter E., 1896-1963 (Box 4, Item JWPB224)
  - Maria Tallchief and André Eglevsky in the Nutcracker, 1954, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Fehl, Fred (Box 4, Item JWPB225)
  - Miguel Terekhov, undated, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 4, Item JWPB226)
  - Tamara Toumonova as Odette in Swan Lake, undated, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 4, Item JWPB227)
  - Tamara Toumonova and Anton Dolin in Giselle, undated, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 4, Item JWPB228)
  - Antony Tudor, 1955, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Kesslàre, G. Maillard (George Maillard) (Box 4, Item JWPB229)
  - Galina Ulanova feeding candy to her goat, Mashka, undated, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Mazelev, R (Box 4, Item JWPB230)
  - Galina Ulanova and Nicolai Fadeyechev in Giselle, 1956, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 4, Item JWPB231)
  - Galina Ulanova and Nicolai Fadeyechev in Giselle, 1956, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 4, Item JWPB232)
  - Galina Ulanova as Giselle, 1956, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 4, Item JWPB233)
  - Galina Ulanova, Nicolai Fadeyechev, and Maya Samokhvalova in Giselle, Act II, 1956, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 4, Item JWPB234)
  - Galina Ulanova and Nicolai Fadeyechev in Giselle, 1956, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 4, Item JWPB235)
  - Galina Ulanova and Nicolai Fadeyechev in Giselle, 1956, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 4, Item JWPB236)
  - Galina Ulanova as the Dying Swan, 1956, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 4, Item JWPB237)
  - Galina Ulanova as the Dying Swan, 1956, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 4, Item JWPB238)
  - Galina Ulanova and Iuri Zhdanov in Romeo and Juliet, 1956, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 4, Item JWPB239)
  - Patricia Wilde in Pas de Trois, 1955, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 4, Item JWPB240)
  - Patricia Wilde, undated, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Owen, Walter E., 1896-1963 (Box 4, Item JWPB241)
  - Patricia Wilde and Herbert Bliss in Symphony in C, undated, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Fehl, Fred (Box 4, Item JWPB242)
  - Patricia Wilde and Herbert Bliss in Symphony in C, undated, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Fehl, Fred (Box 4, Item JWPB243)
  - Igor Youskevitch, 1953, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Seymour, Maurice, 1904- (Box 4, Item JWPB244)
  - Igor Youskevitch, 1956, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 4, Item JWPB245)
  - Alicia Alonso and Igor Youskevitch in Don Quixote, undated, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 4, Item JWPB246)
  - Alicia Alonso and Igor Youskevitch in Giselle, undated, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 4, Item JWPB247)
  - Alicia Alonso as Odile and Igor Youskevitch as Prince Siegfried in Black Swan Pas de deux, undated, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 4, Item JWPB248)
  - Igor Youskevitch, undated, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 4, Item JWPB249)
  - Susanna Zviagina, A. Nersesova, Iaroslav Sekh, and German Sitnikov in the Spanish Dance from the Nutcracker, 1956, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 4, Item JWPB250)
- Productions, circa 1910-1960, II.; Box 5 (Items 251-300)
  Arranged alphabetically by city of location.
  - Yugoslav Ballet performing in Athens, Aug. 7, 1957, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Harissiadis, D. A (Box 5, Item JWPB251)
  - Yugoslav Ballet performing in Athens, Aug. 7, 1957, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Harissiadis, D. A (Box 5, Item JWPB252)
  - Performance of Bodas de Sangre (Federico García Lorca's Blood Wedding) at the Teatro Colón, Buenos Aires, 1956, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 5, Item JWPB253)
  - Performance of Checkmate by Sadler's Wells Ballet, undated, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 5, Item JWPB254)
  - Performance of the Firebird by Sadler's Wells Ballet at Royal Opera House, Covent Garden, 1954, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Rogers, Houston (Box 5, Item JWPB255)
  - Performance of Homage to the Queen by Sadler's Wells Ballet at Royal Opera House, Covent Garden, 1953, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Rogers, Houston (Box 5, Item JWPB256)
  - Performance of Le Lac de Cygnes by Sadler's Wells Ballet, undated, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 5, Item JWPB257)
  - Performance of Petrouchka by the Royal Ballet, 1957, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Wood, Roger (Box 5, Item JWPB258)
  - Performance of The Sleeping Beauty, Act I by Sadler's Wells Ballet, undated, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; LeBlang, Sedge (Box 5, Item JWPB259)
  - Performance of The Sleeping Beauty by the Royal Ballet, 1959?, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 5, Item JWPB260)
  - Performance of The Sleeping Beauty by the Royal Ballet, 1959?, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 5, Item JWPB261)
  - Performance of The Sleeping Beauty by the Royal Ballet, 1959?, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 5, Item JWPB262)
  - Performance of The Sleeping Beauty by the Royal Ballet, 1959?, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 5, Item JWPB263)
  - Performance of Solitaire by Sadler's Wells Ballet, 1956, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; McBean, Angus, 1904- (Box 5, Item JWPB264)
  - Performance of Les Sylphides by Ballet Russes de Monte Carlo, undated, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 5, Item JWPB265)
  - Performance of Romeo and Juliet by the Bolshoi Ballet, undated, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 5, Item JWPB266)
  - Performance of Romeo and Juliet by the Bolshoi Ballet, undated, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 5, Item JWPB267)
  - Performance of Romeo and Juliet by the Bolshoi Ballet, undated, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 5, Item JWPB268)
  - Curtain call for Bolshoi Ballet performance of Polonaise and cracovienne, 1956, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 5, Item JWPB269)
  - Performance of Romeo and Juliet by the Bolshoi Ballet, undated, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 5, Item JWPB270)
  - Performance by Moiseyev Dance Company, undated, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 5, Item JWPB271)
  - Performance by Moiseyev Dance Company, with soloist V. Noskov in Vesnyanki, undated, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 5, Item JWPB272)
  - Women dancers of the Moiseyev Dance Company, undated, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 5, Item JWPB273)
  - Performance by Moiseyev Dance Company, with soloist A. Borzov in Vesnyanki, undated, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 5, Item JWPB274)
  - Performance by Moiseyev Dance Company, with soloist L. Golovanov in The Partisans, undated, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 5, Item JWPB275)
  - Performance of Les Sylphides by the American Ballet Theatre, undated, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 5, Item JWPB276)
  - Performance of Agon by New York City Ballet, 1957, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Fehl, Fred (Box 5, Item JWPB277)
  - Performance of Agon by New York City Ballet, 1957, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Fehl, Fred (Box 5, Item JWPB278)
  - Performance of Agon by New York City Ballet, 1957, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Fehl, Fred (Box 5, Item JWPB279)
  - Performance of Allegro Brillante by the New York City Ballet, 1956, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Fehl, Fred (Box 5, Item JWPB280)
  - Performance of Bourrée fantasque by the New York City Ballet, 1949, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Wood, Roger (Box 5, Item JWPB281)
  - Performance of Bourrée fantasque by the New York City Ballet, 1949, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 5, Item JWPB282)
  - Performance of Concerto Barocco by the New York City Ballet, 1951, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Wood, Roger (Box 5, Item JWPB283)
  - Performance of Concerto Barocco by the New York City Ballet, 1951, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Wood, Roger (Box 5, Item JWPB284)
  - Performance of Concerto Barocco by the New York City Ballet, 1951, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Wood, Roger (Box 5, Item JWPB285)
  - Performance of Concerto Barocco by the New York City Ballet, 1951, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Wood, Roger (Box 5, Item JWPB286)
  - Performance of Concerto Barocco by the New York City Ballet, 1951, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Wood, Roger (Box 5, Item JWPB287)
  - Performance of Divertimento No. 15 by the New York City Ballet, 1956, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Fehl, Fred (Box 5, Item JWPB288)
  - Performance of Fanfare by the New York City Ballet, 1953, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 5, Item JWPB289)
  - Performance of The Nutcracker by the New York City Ballet: Spanish Dance scene, 1954, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Fehl, Fred (Box 5, Item JWPB290)
  - Performance of The Nutcracker by the New York City Ballet, 1954, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Fehl, Fred (Box 5, Item JWPB291)
  - Performance of The Nutcracker by the New York City Ballet, 1954, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Fehl, Fred (Box 5, Item JWPB292)
  - Performance of The Nutcracker by the New York City Ballet, 1954, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Melton, Frederick (Box 5, Item JWPB293)
  - Performance of Orpheus by the New York City Ballet, undated, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 5, Item JWPB294)
  - Performance of Serenade by the New York City Ballet, undated, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 5, Item JWPB295)
  - Performance of Serenade by the New York City Ballet, undated, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 5, Item JWPB296)
  - Performance of The Unicorn, the Gorgon, and the Manticore by the New York City Ballet, 1957, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Fehl, Fred (Box 5, Item JWPB297)
  - Performance of The Unicorn, the Gorgon, and the Manticore by the New York City Ballet, 1957, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Fehl, Fred (Box 5, Item JWPB298)
  - Performance of The Unicorn, the Gorgon, and the Manticore by the New York City Ballet, 1957, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Fehl, Fred (Box 5, Item JWPB299)
  - Performance of Western Symphony by the New York City Ballet, 1955, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Fehl, Fred (Box 5, Item JWPB300)
Search Terms
The following terms have been used to index the description of this collection in the Library's online catalog.
Subjects
Ballet--Photographs; Ballet companies--Photographs; Ballet dancers--Photographs; New York City Ballet--Photographs; Royal Ballet--Photographs; Ballet Russe de Monte Carlo--Photographs; Sadler's Wells Ballet--Photographs; Bolshoi teatr SSSR. Balet--Photographs
Genres
Portraits; Black-and-white photographs; Photographs
Associated Material
Related Resources
Related Resources in the Music Library
J. Warren Perry Collection of Photographs, circa 1910-1971
Mus. Arc. 3.1
Chiefly photographs of opera singers and productions, with additional photographs of other musicians, ensembles, and performing venues.